<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joseph Early</title>
    <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joseph Early</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 15:03:26 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.jearly.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 15:03:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/publications/</guid>
      <description>University of Southampton; PhD Thesis&#xA;June 2024&#xA;Interpretable Multiple Instance Learning Joseph Early&#xA;With the rising use of Artifcial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) methods, there comes an increasing need to understand how automated systems make decisions. Interpretable ML provides insight into the underlying reasoning behind AI and ML models while not stifing their predictive performance. Doing so is important for many reasons, such as facilitating trust, increasing transparency, and providing improved collaboration and control through a better understanding of automated decision-making.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 13:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/projects/</guid>
      <description>Github, Joseph Early&#xA;November 2023&#xA;MIL for Time Series Classification Code for my paper &#34;Inherently Interpretable Time Series Classification via Multiple Instance Learning&#34;.&#xA;Github, Joseph Early&#xA;October 2023&#xA;Tidy Tuesday - Taylor Swift Write-up for a Tidy Tuesday data visualization project exploring if Taylor Swift lyrics follow Zipf&#39;s law.&#xA;Github, Joseph Early&#xA;November 2022&#xA;MIL for Land Cover Classification Code for my paper &#34;Scene-to-Patch Earth Observation: Multiple Instance Learning for Land Cover Classification&#34;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 15:03:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description> Full Name Email Address Message </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 15:03:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/articles/</guid>
      <description>DMsGuild, Joseph Early&#xA;January 2024&#xA;Desires of Emberfeld Embark on an unforgettable journey in Desires of Emberfeld, a riveting one-shot Dungeons &amp; Dragons adventure.&#xA;Medium - Level Up Coding, Joseph Early&#xA;March 2023&#xA;Mastering Subplot Legends in Matplotlib A tutorial on how to create shared subplot legends in Matplotlib. Python code provided in a Jupyter notebook.&#xA;Newsweek, Pandora Dewan&#xA;March 2023 Scientists Are Now Teaching AI How To Read Human Minds Artificial Intelligence (AI) can read your mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 14:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Bio Joseph is currently an AI Research Engineer at Helsing - AI to serve our democracies. He completed a PhD with the University of Southampton and the Alan Turing Institute, and an Integrated MEng Computer Science degree at the University of Southampton, specialising in machine learning. He was awarded a first-class degree, and won the Winton Capital Management Prize for top student in Computer Science and the prize for best Master&#39;s Project.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
