<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joseph Early</title>
    <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joseph Early</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language><atom:link href="https://www.jearly.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 15:03:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/publications/</guid>
      <description>SCRIPTed: A Journal of Law, Technology, and Society February 2023 A Risk-based Approach to AI Regulation: System Categorisation and Explainable AI Practices Keri Grieman, Joseph Early The regulation of artificial intelligence (AI) presents a challenging new legal frontier that is only just beginning to be addressed around the world. This article provides an examination of why regulation of AI is difficult, with a particular focus on understanding the reasoning behind automated decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 13:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/projects/</guid>
      <description>Github, Joseph Early November 2022 MIL for Land Cover Classification Code for my paper &#34;Scene-to-Patch Earth Observation: Multiple Instance Learning for Land Cover Classification&#34; (NeurIPS 2022: Workshop on Tackling Climate Change with Machine Learning). Github, Joseph Early June 2022 MIL for Non-Markovian Reward Modelling Code for my paper &#34;Non-Markovian Reward Modelling from Trajectory Labels via Interpretable Multiple Instance Learning&#34; (NeurIPS 2022). Github, Joseph Early January 2022 MILLI - Multiple Instance Learning Local Interpretations Code for my paper &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 15:03:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description> Full Name Email Address Message </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 15:03:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/articles/</guid>
      <description>Medium - Level Up Coding, Joseph Early March 2023 Mastering Subplot Legends in Matplotlib Matplotlib subplots allow you to show several different graphs within a single figure. However, it is often nice to have a shared legend that provides detail on the information displayed in the subplots. In this article, I explain how to create shared legends, and format them to nicely arrange your subplots. The code used to generate of all the plots shown is included in a Python Notebook at the end of this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 14:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Bio Joseph is a doctoral student with the University of Southampton and the Alan Turing Institute. He completed an undergraduate degree in computer science at the University of Southampton, and then specialised with a master’s degree focused on machine learning (also at the University of Southampton). Joseph pursued his interest in machine learning and is now in the third year of his PhD. His research focuses on interpretable machine learning – the process of unpacking the “black box” of artificial intelligence and understanding why models exhibit certain behaviours.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
