<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joseph Early</title>
    <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joseph Early</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language><atom:link href="https://www.jearly.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 15:03:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/publications/</guid>
      <description>NeurIPS 2022 October 2022 Non-Markovian Reward Modelling from Trajectory Labels via Interpretable Multiple Instance Learning Joseph Early, Tom Bewley, Christine Evers, Sarvapali Ramchurn We generalise the problem of reward modelling (RM) for reinforcement learning (RL) to handle non-Markovian rewards. Existing work assumes that human evaluators observe each step in a trajectory independently when providing feedback on agent behaviour. In this work, we remove this assumption, extending RM to include hidden state information that captures temporal dependencies in human assessment of trajectories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 13:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/projects/</guid>
      <description>Github, Joseph Early June 2022 MIL for Non-Markovian Reward Modelling Code for my paper &#34;Non-Markovian Reward Modelling from Trajectory Labels via Interpretable Multiple Instance Learning&#34;. Github, Joseph Early January 2022 MILLI - Multiple Instance Learning Local Interpretations Code for my paper &#34;Model Agnostic Interpretability for Multiple Instance Learning&#34; (ICLR 2022). Github, Joseph Early June 2020 LatexTable - A Python library for creating Latex tables Texttable is a Python package that can create simple ASCII tables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 15:03:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description> Full Name Email Address Message </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 15:03:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/articles/</guid>
      <description>The Conversation, Joseph Early October 2022 AI could help predict suicides – but rushing the technology could lead to big mistakes AI has great potential to save the lives of mental health patients, but care must be taken to ensure it&#39;s used safely and correctly. A study conducted in October 2022, led by the Black Dog Institute in the University of New South Wales, found artificial intelligence (AI) models outperformed clinical risk assessments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.jearly.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 14:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jearly.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Bio Joseph is a doctoral student with the University of Southampton and the Alan Turing Institute. He completed an undergraduate degree in computer science at the University of Southampton, and then specialised with a master’s degree focused on machine learning (also at the University of Southampton). Joseph pursued his interest in machine learning and is now in the third year of his PhD. His research focuses on interpretable machine learning – the process of unpacking the “black box” of artificial intelligence and understanding why models exhibit certain behaviours.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
